const quizData = [
  {
    question: 'What is the oldest U.S. national park?',
    answers: [
      'Great Smoky Mountains National Park',
      'Grand Canyon National Park',
      'Yellowstone National Park',
      'Big Bend National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Yellowstone National Park',
    fact: 'The first national park was founded in 1872'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which national park is home to the world\'s tallest tree?',
    answers: [
      'Redwood National Park',
      'Sequoia National Park',
      'Everglades National Park',
      'Cuyahoga Valley National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Redwood National Park',
    fact: 'Named Hyperion, it is recognized by the Guinness Book of World Records'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which state has the most national parks?',
    answers: [
      'Alaska',
      'Utah',
      'Montana',
      'California'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'California',
    fact: 'Alaska and California used to be tied with eight each until Pinnacles became a national park in CA in 2013'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the smallest national park?',
    answers: [
      'Isle Royale National Park',
      'Hot Springs National Park',
      'Katmai National Park',
      'Pinnacles National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Hot Springs National Park',
    fact: 'It is about 5500 acres and the first federally protected piece of land in 1832'
  },
  {
    question: 'What animal killed a man in 2010 in Olympic National Park?',
    answers: [
      'Elk',
      'Bear',
      'Goat',
      'Cougar'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Goat',
    fact: 'These goats are not a native species to the region'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which national park was created during the Great Depression?',
    answers: [
      'Shenandoah National Park',
      'Gates of the Artic National Park',
      'Petrified Forest National Park',
      'Dry Tortugas National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Shenandoah National Park',
    fact: 'It was built by members of the Civilian Conservation Corps'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which national park is one of the Seven Natural Wonders of the World?',
    answers: [
      'Yosemite National Park',
      'Zion National Park',
      'Grand Canyon National Park',
      'Sequoia National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Grand Canyon National Park',
    fact: 'However, it was previously called the Big Canyon or the Great Canyon'
  },
  {
    question: 'The National Park Services protects over __ ________ acres of wild landscapes and historic sites.',
    answers: [
      '42 million',
      '84 million',
      '239 million',
      '171 million'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '84 million',
    fact: 'Parks rangers also educate visitors about park history, natural features, wildlife, and conservation'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which national park recorded one of the hottest temperatures on earth in 1913?',
    answers: [
      'Death Valley National Park',
      'Badlands National Park',
      'Hawaii Volcanoes National Park',
      'Mesa Verde National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Death Valley National Park',
    fact: 'The temperature registered at 134 degrees'
  },
  {
    question: 'What national park is the most visited every year?',
    answers: [
      'Yellowstone National Park',
      'Mount Ranier National Park',
      'Grand Canyon National Park',
      'Great Smoky Mountains National Park'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Great Smoky Mountains National Park',
    fact: 'More than 9 million guests visit every year'
  }
];
